Guide to the Development Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Development Office, Yale School of Drama, records
1925-2000
RU 730
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
33.25
The records consist of correspondence, financial summaries, donor lists, reports, agreements, job announcements, faculty biographies, grants and scholarships, and committee notes documenting the activities and operations of the Development Office of the Yale School of Drama. Included are records concerning a Yale salute to Cole Porter at Carnegie Hall, ca. 1984.
Yale School of Drama
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-E (YRG 22-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, financial summaries, donor lists, reports, agreements, job announcements, faculty biographies, grants and scholarships, and committee notes documenting the activities and operations of the Development Office of the Yale School of Drama. Included are records concerning a Yale salute to Cole Porter at Carnegie Hall, ca. 1984.
Educational fund raising; Fund raising; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Finance; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Finance
- Records of the Development Office, 1925-1983; Accession 1986-A-026
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Correspondence, 1943-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Class Agents, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Results by Years, 1953-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class Agents, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Formation and Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
  - Articles of Organization and Procedures, 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Elbert A. Gruver, Chairmen, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Convocation, "C-Note Club", 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: E. Lawrence Goodman, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Organizational, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Bequest Program, 1960-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Earmarked Gifts, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Campaign, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Campaign, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Campaign, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Preparatory Letters, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Capital Campaign Information, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Campaign, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Preliminaries, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Campaign, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Preliminaries, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Organization and Procedures, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Campaign, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Class Agents, Enrollment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Agents' Kits, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Class Agent Letters, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Regional Agents enrollment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Campaign: Analysis, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Preliminaries, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Prospects, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Convocation, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Thanks Notes, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Yale Alumni Fund Historian Notes, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Alumni Concern, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Campaign: Analysis, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Campaign: Miscellaneous, Data Storage and Retrieval, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Letters to Agents, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Class Agents, Preliminaries, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Gifts, Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Special Gifts, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Thanks, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Weekly Reports, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Class Agents: First Letters, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Convocation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Preliminaries, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Regional Agents, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Special Gifts, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Status Reports, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Thanks Notes, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Berfmann Data: Analysis, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Class Agents: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Special Gifts, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Memorial Gifts, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Thanks Notes, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Campaign: Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Final Tallies, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Agent List, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Campaign Mailings, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Class Agents, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Running Tallies and Analyses, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Special Gifts, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Campaign Mailings, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Class Agents: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Class Agents, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous: By Class, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Corresppndence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Running Tallies and Analyses, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Special Gifts, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Status Report, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Thank-You Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Drama Class Agent Lists, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Campaign Mailings, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Class Agents: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Class Agents, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Final Report, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Regional, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Running Analyses, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Work Folder, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Special Gifts, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Campaign, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Campaign Mailings, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Agents List, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Final Gift Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Regional, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Running Analyses, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Special Gifts, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA), 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Status Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Final Reports, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Campaign Letters, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Drama Alumni Association, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Status Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Final Reports, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Phone-Mail, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - AYA Assembly, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Convocation, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Agent Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 118 - 119)
  - Yale Drama Alumni Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Alumni Materials, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Thank You's, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Convocation, undated (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Drama Alumni Newsletter, 1954-1962 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - 1970-1978 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Drama Alumni Newsletter: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Correspondence, Copies of Forestry and Nursing Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Volume II, Number 3 (Alumni Directory), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - ABC (TV), 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Alliance Theatre, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - American Playhouse, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - American Theatre Association: Commonwealth Awards, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Kennedy Center Black Theatre Project Task Force, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 143 - 144)
    - Giving Lists, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Antique Costume Collection, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Applicants, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, undated (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Audience Survey: Preliminary Results for Subscribers, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Benefits, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Benefit, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 154 - 155)
  - Plans for a Benefit at the University Theatre, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Board of Theatre Perspectives: Audrey Cooper (CUNY), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Booth, John: Independent Committee on Arts Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Cable Television, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 165)
    - 1978 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - CBS Cable: Lady Lester (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Center for Music, Drama, Art: Advisory Selection Panel for Fellowships, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Century Club Luncheon, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Computer Systems, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Conferences and Consultants, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Conference on Television, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Connecticut Arts Awards, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 175 - 176)
  - Contributions, 1965, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Contributor List, Yale Rep. Program, Dodger Theatre Program, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Corporations, Research on: Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Corporate Group Sales, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous "A", 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Miscellaneous "B", 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous "C", 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Edward Cole: Correspondence and Notes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous "D", 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Deferred Giving Plans, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - DeNardis, Larry: U.S. Representative, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Department Projects, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 189)
  - Development Director: Sidney Baker, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 190 - 191)
  - Office: Director of Development, undated (Box 15, Folder 192 - 193)
  - Drama School Informational Packet, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Dramatist's Guild, undated (Box 16, Folder 195)
  - Electro-Mechanical Lab Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 196)
  - Endowment Drive, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  - Eulogy for Marc Connelly, 50th Anniversary, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 198)
  - Finances, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  - Gift Opportunities, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 208)
  - Special Gifts Campaign, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  - Guides to Fellowships, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Handicapped Access, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Home Box Office (HBO), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  - Rowland, C.P.: California Development Director, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 213)
  - Individual Prospects to be Researched, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 214)
  - International Theatre Festival, Proposal for, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Job Openings, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 216)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 217)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 218 - 220)
    - Permanent, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 222 - 223)
    - Summer, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 224)
      - Filled, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 225)
    - Referrals, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Junior League and Other Volunteers, 1968-1981 (Box 18, Folder 227)
  - League of Professional Theatre: Training Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Lighting Equipment, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 230)
  - Media Production Unit, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 231)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Organizational Lists of Corporate Donors, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Cole Porter, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Press List: Fundraising, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Program Notes, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 236)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 237)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - Proposal Status Report, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Rejected Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Reviews, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Scholarship Statistics, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Scholarships and Named Prizes, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - "Shopping List" of Projects, 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Sondheim Project, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Status of University Proposals, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - "Theatre" Magazine: Budgets and General, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Theatre Studies, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Richard Ward Scholarship, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Warner Brothers, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Constance Welch Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 253)
  - Rebecca West Scholarship, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 254)
  - Winterfest, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Dinners, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Yale Drama Faculty: Biographies, 1954-1969 (Box 19, Folder 258)
  - Yale University: Western Office, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 259)
  - Youngberg, C.W.: Miscellaneous Development Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - American Arts Alliance, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 262 - 263)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - Advocate, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 265)
  - American Broadcasting Companies (ABC): Grants, 1967-1979 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - 1980 (Box 20, Folder 267)
  - Atlantic Richfield Foundation: Pitch Letter, Negative Response, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - George Pierce Baker Scholarship, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - CBS, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - CBS Fellows, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 273)
  - Columbia Pictures, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Connecticut Advocates for the Arts, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 277)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 278)
    - 1976-1982 (Box 21, Folder 279)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 280)
    - 1983 (Box 21, Folder 281)
    - Bicentennial Grant, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 282)
    - "The Frogs", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 283)
    - "Happy End" Music Expenses, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Operational Aid, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts: Operational Aid, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 286)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 287)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 288)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 289)
    - "Funtila" (Box 22, Folder 290)
    - Submissions (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - "Troilus and Cressida" (Box 22, Folder 292)
  - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 293)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 294)
  - Exxon, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 299)
  - Ford Grant, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - Ford Report, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 315)
  - John Gassner Memorial Prize, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 318)
  - Yale Cabaret: Gifts, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - Annie Garland Memorial Scholarship, undated (Box 24, Folder 320)
  - Sherwin M. Goldman Productions, undated (Box 24, Folder 323)
  - Gulf and Western Industries: Pitch Letter, Negative Response, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 325)
  - Hartford National Bank, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 326)
  - ITT Travel Grants, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 329)
  - Molly Kazan Prize, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Lake Systems, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs: Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 338)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Lilly Endowment: Research on, Correspondence with, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Charles Matlock Award, undated (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Mellon Foundation, 1974-1983 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - MGM (Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer)/Brendon Ward, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Nagler, Alois M.: Prize, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - National Arts Club: Joseph Kesselring Awards for Playwrights: Announcement of Contest, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - NBC, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 354)
    - Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 355)
    - Administration Grant Request, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    - Administration Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Applications, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 358)
    - 1983 (Box 26, Folder 359)
    - "Director Fellowship", 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 360)
    - Artistic Associate, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 361)
    - Challenge Grant Application: Analysis of Gifts and Grants, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 362)
      - Budget Process, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 363)
    - Challenge Grants, 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 364 - 365)
      - Contributor Analysis, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 366)
      - Faculty List, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 367)
    - Challenge Proposal, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - Challenge Grant Application: Yale Drama School? Repertory Theatre, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - Design Demonstration: Grant Application, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 371)
    - Directing Fellowships, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - "Director Fellowship", 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - Dramaturg Program, 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - Education Program, Arts Administration, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - Grants, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 376)
    - Grant from Play Publication Program, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 377)
    - Administration: Grant Request, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 378)
    - Institutional Advancement Pilot Program, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 379)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 381)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 382)
      - 1983 (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Opera/Musical Theatre, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Professional Theatre Training Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 385)
    - Residencies for Playwrights Program, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 386)
    - Summer Internships, 1974-1981 (Box 27, Folder 387)
    - Theatre, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 388)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 389)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 390)
    - Large Theatre, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 391)
    - "Theatre" Magazine, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 393)
    - 1977-1981 (Box 28, Folder 394)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 395)
    - Grants, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 396)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 397)
    - Script Analysis Project, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 398)
    - Youth Project, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 399)
  - National Development Council, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - National Opera Institute, Kennedy Center, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 401)
  - New Haven Foundation, undated (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 403)
  - Donald Oenslager Scholarship, 1975-1982 (Box 29, Folder 405)
  - O'Neill Theatre Center and Scholarship, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 406)
  - Paramount Pictures Corporation: Pitch Letter, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Polygram Pictures: Possible Grant Requests, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Philip Morris Incorporated: Pitch Letter, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 409)
  - Press Office Opening Night List (Doll's House, Oct. a, 1982) (Box 29, Folder 410)
  - RCA-NBC Fellowships and Scholarships, 1954-1967 (Box 29, Folder 411 - 412)
  - RCA: Research on, Pitch Letter, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 413)
  - RKO/Nederlander: Possible Project, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 414)
  - Scholarships: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 430)
  - Shirin D. Trainer Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 434)
  - Kenneth Tynan Prize, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 435)
  - United Technologies Corporation: Pitch Letter, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 436)
  - Leon Brooks Walker Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 437)
  - Audrey Wood Scholarship, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 439)
  - Alumni Association: Class Secretaries, etc., 1939-1944 (Box 31, Folder 440)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, Graduate and Professional Schools: Receptions, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 441)
  - Yale Dramat Alumni Association: Yale Drama Festival Program, 1974-1980 (Box 31, Folder 442)
  - Yale Alumni Board, 1952-1970 (Box 31, Folder 443)
    - Film Committee, 1955-1963 (Box 31, Folder 444)
  - Alumni Bulletin, 1945-1950 (Box 31, Folder 445)
  - Alumni Fund Status Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 446)
  - Alumni Lists: by Class, 1925-1943 (Box 31, Folder 447)
    - by Class and State, 1926-1953 (Box 31, Folder 448)
  - Drama School Class Lists, 1927-1934 (Box 31, Folder 449)
    - 1935-1945 (Box 31, Folder 450)
  - Drama Alumni Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 451)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 31, Folder 452)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 453)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 454)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 455)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 456)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 457)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 458)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 459)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 460)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 461)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 462)
    - 1961 (Box 32, Folder 463)
  - Drama Alumni Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 464)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 465)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 466)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 467)
  - Alumni Contacts Lists, undated (Box 32, Folder 468)
  - Alumni Dinner, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 469)
    - 1945 (Box 32, Folder 470)
    - 1946 (Box 32, Folder 471)
    - 1947 (Box 33, Folder 472)
    - 1948 (Box 33, Folder 473)
  - Alumni Directory, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 474)
    - 1925-1939 (Box 33, Folder 475)
  - Alumni Luncheon, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 476)
  - Notable Alumni, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 477)
  - Alumni Notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 478)
    - 1948-1954 (Box 33, Folder 479)
  - Alumni, Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 480)
  - Alumni Records Information, undated (Box 33, Folder 481)
  - Alumni Reports, undated (Box 33, Folder 482)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 483)
  - University Theatre Alumni List, 1925-1943 (Box 34, Folder 485)
    - By State, 1925-1943 (Box 34, Folder 486)
  - The 47 Workshop Group: Harvard University, Circa 1938 (Box 34, Folder 487)
  - World War II: Record of Drama People, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 488)
- Records concerning Yale salute to Cole Porter at Carnegie Hall, circa 1984-1985; Accession 1993-A-086
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020
  - Benefit, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Plans, Schedules, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Hall Rental, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Contact Sheets, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Corporate Underwriting Proposals, Corporate Prospect Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Drama School Names, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 13)
  - Fact Sheets, Mission, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Film Clearances, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Slides and Film Production, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Film Information, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)